Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Clippings File, 1962-1987; 8; 12 cubic ft.
  - CPES, 1964; 1976; 1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 66)
  - CPES Taxpayer, 1975 January-1975 February (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 67)
  - County Committee Organization -- CPNYS, 1964 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68)
  - CSEA, 1972 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 69)
  - C.U.N.Y., 1971-1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 70)
  - Cuomo, Gov. Mario, 1986 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 71)
  - Cuomo, Gov. Mario, 1988 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 72)
  - Election Results -- NYC Mayoral, 1969 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 73)
  - Election Results, 1972 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 74)
  - Election Results, 1973 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 75)
  - Election Results, 1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 76)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1975-1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 77)
  - Esposito, John, 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 78)
  - Farms, 1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 79)
  - Federal Attorneys, 1975 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 80)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 81)
  - Federalist Papers, 1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 82)
  - Gay Rights, Undated (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 83)
  - Florida Primary, 1972 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - Garn, Jake, 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - Garth, David, 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - Heroin, 1974 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - House Unanimous Act, 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - I (Insurance, etc), 1977-1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - Israel, 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - Labor, 1972-1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - Labor Day, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - Lance, Bert, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - Landlord & Tenant, 1978; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - Lane, Franklin. H.S., Cypress Hills, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - Langley, 1972 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - Latin America -- General, 1963-1965; 1977; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - Laurino, Louis, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - Law, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 17)
  - Law -- "Blue Laws", 1975; 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - Law -- Class Actions, 1971 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - "Law Day", 1971 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - Laws -- Drugs, 1972-1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - Law Enforcement, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - Law -- Exclusionary Rule, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - Law -- Grand Jury, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - Law -- Kidnapping, 1974 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - Law -- Privilege, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - Law -- Rape, 1973-1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - Law -- Search & Seizure, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - Law -- Sentencing, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - Lawyers, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - Lawyers' Conference, 1974 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - Lee, Grady, 1978; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - Leff, James, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis, 1976-1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - Leftist Organizations, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - Legal Services, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - Legislative Reform -- Federal, 1972; 1974; 1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - Legislative Reform -- NYS, 1972; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - Legislature, 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - Lenti, Norman, 1973; 1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - Lewis, Larry, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - Levitt, Arthur, 1972 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43)
  - Levitt, Arthur, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 44)
  - Levitt, Arthur, 1972-1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 45)
  - Libel Suits, 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - Libertarian Party, 1972-1979 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - Liberty Conservative Club (Ozone Park), 1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - Lt. Governor, 1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - Lt. Governor's Administration, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - Lt. Governor's Staff, 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - Lindsay, John, 1971 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - Lindsay, John, 1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - Lindsay, John -- Press Clippings, 1964-1966 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - Lindsay, Mayor John, 1970-1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - Liquor Law Reform, 1964 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - Lobbyists, 1973-1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - Local Government, 1972 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - Loeb, John, 1979 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - Loeb, William, 1973; 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - Lombardi, Tarky, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - Lomenzo, John, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 63)
  - Long Island City, 1976-1977; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 64)
  - Long Island Expressway, 1967 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 65)
  - Long Island Politics, 1972-1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 66)
  - Long Island Railroad, 1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 67)
  - Looting, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68)
  - Lottery, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 69)
  - Lowenstein, Allard, 1968; 1972-1974; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 70)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1974; 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 71)
  - Lugar, Richard, 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 72)
  - "Lulus", 1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 73)
  - Mackell, Thomas, 1972-1974 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 74)
  - MacLaine, Shirley, 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 75)
  - Mail Registration, 1975-1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 76)
  - Maine, 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 77)
  - Malerba, Mario, 1979 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 78)
  - Malpractice, 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 79)
  - Maltese, Serphin R., 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 80)
  - Mandatory Sentence, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 81)
  - Manes, Donald, 1971-1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 82)
  - Manhattan Boro President, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 83)
  - Manton, Thomas, 1972-1974 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 84)
  - Marchi, John, 1969-1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 85)
  - Margiotta, Joseph, 1972-1976; 1980 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 86)
  - Marijuana, 1971-1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 87)
  - Marijuana -- Decriminalization, 1971; 1977-1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 88)
  - Marijuana Fight -- NYS Legislative HQS. File, 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 89)
  - Marston, David, 1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 90)
  - Mason, Edwyn, 1973 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 91)
  - Maspeth, 1976-1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 92)
  - Massachusetts, 1978 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 93)
  - Mater Chusti H.S., 1977 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 94)
  - Maternal & Child Health Act, 1976 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 95)
  - Matthew, Dr. Thomas, 1973; 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 96)
  - Mayaguez, 1975 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 97)
  - Mayoral, 1969 (Box 3 (8-Clippings File), Folder 98)
  - Mayor, 1981 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - Mayor's Administration, 1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - Mayor's Staff, 1973-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - Mayor's Staff, 1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - Mayoral, 1977; 3 folders (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5-7)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1975-1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - McCloskey, Pete, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - McCormack, Ellen, 1975-1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - McDonald, Hon. Larry, 1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - McFarland, James, 1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - McGovern, George, 1972-1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - Media, 1974-1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - Medicaid, 1966-1968 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - Medicaid, 1971-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 17)
  - Medicaid Abortion, 1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - Medicare, 1977; 1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - Mental Agency, 1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - Mental Hygiene, 1972-1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - Metric System, Undated (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - Mexico, 1977-1979 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - Meyer, Frank, 1971; 1973; 1975 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - MIAs, 1974-1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - Middendorf, Henry, 1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - Mid-East, 1975-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - Migrant Workers, 1975 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - Milano, Robert, 1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - Military, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - Military Academics, 1969; 1972 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - Military Unions, 1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - Miller, William, 1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - Miner, Ken, 1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - Minimum Wage, 1971-1974; 1978-1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - Minnesota, 1971 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - Minorities, 1971-1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - Mississippi, 1975 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - Mitchell, John, 1974 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - Mitchell - Lama, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - Mitchell, Timothy, 1972 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - Mobilization for Youth, 1972 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - Molinari, Guy, 1981; 1985 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1976-1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 44)
  - Moon, Syung Sun, 1976-1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 45)
  - Monroe County, 1968-1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - Moral Decline (NYC and NYS), 1972; 1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - Morality, 1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - Morgenthal, Robert, 1974 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - Morrow, James, 1973-1974 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - Morse, Robert, 1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - Mortgages, 1973; 1976-1978; 1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - Moses, Robert, 1972; 1974; 1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - MTA (Metropolitan Transit Authority), 1971-1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - Muratori, Jack, 1976-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - Murder, 1969; 1975 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - Murdoch, Rupert, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - Murphy, John, 1978-1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - Murphy, Patrick, 1973 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - Muskie, Edmund, 1972 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - Myerson, Bess, 1973-1974; 1978; 1980 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - N.A.A.C.P., 1975; 1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1973-1979 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 63)
  - Nadjari, Maurice, 1974-1979 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 64)
  - Nassau County, 1971-1976 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 65)
  - Nassau County, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 66)
  - Nassau County Conservative Party, Undated (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 67)
  - National Commission On International Women's Year, 1977 (Box 4 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68)
  - National Defense, 1974-1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - National Health Insurance Plan, 1974-1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - National Lawyers'Guild, 1976 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - National Renaissance Party, Undated (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - National Security, 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - National Security Agency, 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - NATO, 1964; 1971; 1977; 1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - Nazi Party -- U.S., 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - NDC (New Democratic Coalition), 1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood Crime, 1976 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Preservation, 1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - Neutron Bomb, 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - New Democratic Coalition, 1973-1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - New Hampshire, 1972 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - New Hampshire Primary, 1972 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - New Hampshire, 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - New Jersey, 1973-1976 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 17)
  - New Majority, 1976 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - NLRB Legislation, 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - N.O.W. (National Organization for Women), 1975; 1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - New York City, 1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - NYC Agencies, 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - NYC Assistance, 1981 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - NYC Board of Standards & Appeals, Undated (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - NYC Bridges, 1976; 1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - NYC Budget, 1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - NYC Budget, 1981 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - NYC Charter, 1972-1975; 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - NYC Citywide Races, 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - NYC Comptroller, 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - NYC Comptroller, 1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - NYC Comptroller, 1980 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - NYC Convention Center, 1973 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - NYC Convention Center, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - NYC Corruption, 1972-1973 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - NYC Council, 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - NYC Council President, 1971-1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - NYC Decline, 1971-1980 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - NYC Decline, 1981 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - NYC Economy, 1973-1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - NYC Elections -- Mayoral, 1965 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - NYC Elections, 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - NYC Finances, 1975; 3 folders (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43-45)
  - NYC Finances, 1976 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - NYC Finances, 1977 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - NYC Government, 1972; 1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - NYC Finances, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - NYC Law, 1972 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - NYC Officials Pay Raise, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - NYC Organization, 1973 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - NYC Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - NYC Politics, 1976; 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - NYC Residency Law, 1974; 1977-1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - NYC Retirement, 1973 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - NYC Sanitation, Undated (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - NYC Sports Complex, 1973 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - NYC Staff, 1972-1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - NYC Tenant - Landlord, 1974 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - NYC Taxes, 1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - NYC Tolls, 1975-1978 (Box 5 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - NYC Transportation, 1964-1967; 1971-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - NY County, 1971-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - NY County Borough President, 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - New York Express Pilot Issue, 1970 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - New York Post, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - New York State, 1973-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - NYS and US Benefits, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - NYS Appointments & Positions, Undated (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - NYS Assembly, 1975-1979 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - NYS Budget, 1974-1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - NYS Charter, 1975 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - NYS Committee of Investigation, 1979 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - NYS Comptroller, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - NYS Conservative Party Committees, 1972 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - NYS Conservative Party, 1978-1979 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - NYS Conservative Party, 1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - NYS Constitutional Convention, 1969; 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - NYS Constitutional Convention, 1972-1973 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - NYS Council on the Arts, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - NYS Courts, 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - NYS Democratic Party, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - NYS Election Board, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - NYS Election Law, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - NYS Election Law, 1981 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - NYS/NYC Finances, 1971 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - NYS/NYC Finances, 1972 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - NYS/NYC Finances, 1973 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - NYS/NYC Finances, 1974 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - NYS Finances, 1975 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - NYS Finances, 1975 November (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - NYS Finances, 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - NYS Finances, 1978-1979 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - NYS Government, 1979 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - NYS Hiring, 1973-1974 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - NYS Legislation, 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - NYS Legislature Bills, 1972 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - NYS Legislature Bills, 1973 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - NYS Legislature Bills, 1974 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - NYS Legislative Session, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - NYS Legislative Staff, 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - NYS Legislature, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - NYS Legislature, 1979-1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - NYS Legislature Pay Increase, 1972-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43)
  - NYS Legislature Special Session, 1973 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 44)
  - NYS Legislature Special Session, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 45)
  - NYS Legislature Special Session, 1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - NYS Lieutenant Governor, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - NYS North Central Region, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - NYS Pay Increase (State Workers), 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - NYS Politics, 1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - NYS Presidential Delegates, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - NYS Primary, 1972 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - NYS Property Tax, 1977-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - NYS Regional Development, 1964-1965 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - NYS Republican Party, 1976-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - NYS Republican Party, 1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - NYS Senate, 1972-1980 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - NYS Senate Primary, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - NYS Special Prosecutor, 1976 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - NYS Supreme Court Decisions, 1977 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - NYS Taxes, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - NYS Unions, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - NYS Western Regions, 1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 63)
  - News Polls, 1974 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 64)
  - News Shield, 1973 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 65)
  - Niagara County, 1973-1975 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 66)
  - Nicaragua, 1978-1979 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 67)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1971-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1971-1978 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68A)
  - Nixon's Finances, 1973 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 69)
  - Nixon Resignation, 1974 (Box 6 (8-Clippings File), Folder 70)
  - No Fault Insurance, 1971-1978 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - "No Show", 1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - North Carolina, 1976; 1978 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - North Korea, 1979 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Energy, 1979 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - Nurses, 1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - Nursing Homes, 1974-1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - Nyquist, Ewald, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - Obscenity, 1975 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - O'Connor, Frank, 1973 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - O'Doherty, Kiernan, 1964; 1968-1972; 1974-1975 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1968-1971; 1975-1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - OEO (Office of Economic Opportunity), 1969; 1971; 1973 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - Olivieri, Antonio, 1973-1974 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - Olympics, 1977-1980 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - Oneida, 1976 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - Onondaga County, 1968-1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 17)
  - OPEC (Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries), 1975 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - Orange County, 1968; 1974 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - Organization, Undated (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - Orleans County, 1973-1974 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - Organized Crime, 1971-1979 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - OSHA, 1973-1979 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - Oswego County, 1975; 1977; 1980 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - OTB (Off - Track Betting), 1974-1978 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - Ottinger, Richard, 1978; 1980 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - Ozone Layer, 1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - Padavan, Frank, 1972-1974; 1978; 1980 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - P.A.T. (Parents and Taxpayers), 1975 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - Panama Canal, 1975 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - Panama Canal, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - Panama Canal, 1964; 1967; 1973-1978 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - Paolucci, Henry, 1964; 1970; 1973 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - Parking Violations, 1976 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - Parks, 1972; 1976-1980 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - Parkways, 1973 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - Parole, 1977 (Box 7 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)